I had a conversation yesterday it was
somebody the conversation is recorded
but it won't be made public I don't
think it's right to make the public it
doesn't feel right
there's something in there about the
safety for him and not making a public
but in him showing me sharing with me
his shadow I was able to see more of my
light and he also brought up something
that keeps happening within the game be
space which is my name
Jubilee not them saying my name but
using my name in any one of the other
myriad of ways that it is used that
isn't referring to me as a person and so
today I want to do that video what is in
a name
my name is Jubilee I did not choose this
name his name was chosen for me by my
parents in a large part because we were
evangelical Christian all of our names
me and my two siblings come from the
Bible in the Bible the Jubilee is the
year they set the slaves free once every
50 years I believe people would put
themselves or be putting into debt
slavery and that would generally based
on when the year of the Jubilee was I've
had this name my entire life it means
that people generally remember my name
when I don't remember theirs
it's gotten me jobs because I stand out
on a resume but right now the three
things that speak to me about my name
are that it's that thing in the Bible
because four things that it means
celebration
that also becomes synonymous in the game
be space and with more of the new group
of people on not just debt and slaves
being set free but on their actually
being so I think on a threshold of
people involved in something that then
makes it safe so Jordan Hall brought
that up in our conversation that's on my
channel where let's say there is a
deadly but to just stop paying their
debts it's gonna get you landed in jail
or horrible credit score it's not
actually gonna help you world but if
enough people signed up for debt Jubilee
judge both not hold other people's debts
against them or pay off your debts when
enough threshold of people sign up that
could actually occur and so that
threshold it has been come known as a
Jubilee yesterday my conversation
brought up what was a rolling jubilee a
which is the idea that people buy old
debt for pennies on the dollar and then
just forgive it and send out letters to
the people instead of demanding that
they pay it and getting a few more cents
on the dollar they save it's written off
you don't know anything but if you
wanted to donate so we could buy more
debt than you can my necklace the first
piece of my protection jewelry fell off
on my friend Eric's birthday well the
words Jubilee debt Jubilee for being
spoken by Charles Eisenstein I was
watching a video
there's a friend Eric in the game bSpace
maybe that's reading too much into it
but maybe not the third fourth what
number man whatever my fourth Jubilee is
there's a YouTube channel called Jubilee
and on it
they bring two sides of opposing two
opposing sides together to see if they
can find common ground or they ask a
group of people that have something in
common like women or Muslims whether
they agree on an issue how many of them
agree on issues that pertain to that
group
my name is Jubilee I am here to set the
slaves free to cancel the debt and
create a world that works for everyone
and the more I know that I'm not here to
convince you all that on that I'm here
to convince me that I'm not the signs
have to keep piling up how many times do
I have to hear my name come out of
somebody else's mouth in a powerful
format how many clues do I have to get
along the way of how to create game be
knowing the things we can create
together that lead to a world that works
for everyone
my name is Jubilee and I'm getting it
more and more every day as I follow my
own path mine has to be so obvious my
name had to be Jubilee because if I only
knew how to save the world I don't know
if I would trust myself to be the person
but the more I hear it every time it's
just that little push and in every
context it's like the interweaving of
all those things the Christianity the
opposing sides the cancelling of debt
and slavery and celebration we are gonna
do what feels right now like The
Impossible
it doesn't feel impossible to me me
being the person still has a little bit
of good possibility to me
but I'm stepping into it